The world.
What a glorious place.
Seek freedom, and it will lie
stretched out before your eyes.
If the endless dream guides
your restless spirit,
seize it, raise your flag, and stand tall.
I think back to the time
when my search first began.
I left behind those shores of sand.
For the endless everlasting
world out there.
I know that with the
burning passion driving me.
Someday, somewhere, I'll finally see the
light I have searched for everywhere?
When the summer sun is shining.
Shaking the sails of my heart, I know.
You're the way from the sea.
A brand new world that has been hiding.
Has opened up its doors for me to go.
You're the way from the sky.
We're in the troubled ways.
From all despair I can be saved.
For the horizon on the other side is.
And though I've traveled far
from where my search began,
over seas of green and shores of sand,
through the endless
everlasting world out there.
I know that with this
burning passion driving me,
some days somewhere I'll finally see
the light I will search for everywhere.
That old lady ratted us out!
She lied to us.
She said it was okay
for us to pass through.
But when we did, they
accused us of illegal entry?
That's flat-out fraud.
Exactly.
But then, even if we were
told we couldn't pass,
we would have just forced our way through.
I mean, how was that little
old lady going to stop us?
Shut up!
In any case, you're in
a great deal of trouble.
You're now second-degree
criminals, and as such,
I'm afraid Conis and I are
unable to assist you any longer.
Why are you talking to
us from way over there?
I really don't see what the big deal is.
I'm surprised you're
not used to this by now.
I've been meaning to ask.
Why'd you come back, Nami? What?
We were finally gonna get to set sail and
head out on an amazing
adventure until you...
I mean, we were about
to come looking for you.
We were getting worried.
I think you and I need
to have a little talk.
Forget about your big adventure!
It's never gonna happen!
You haven't seen what I've seen!
That island is full of the types of
people you don't want to mess with!
I don't care who you think you are!
Granted, we don't know what this
guy is, but his powers are real!
And there's no way I'm ever
going back there again!
So forget it! Got me?
How about you just relax
here while the rest of us go?
We're wanted criminals!
I'm not staying here a
minute longer either!
Are you nuts?
Get your priorities straight!
The adventure is always
the most important part!
My priorities are life first, then honey!
Please tell me I'm third on that list!
Don't push me!
You raise a good point.
We put all of our energy into
just trying to get up here,
but we never really thought about
how we were going to get back.
Is there a safe way back
to the Blue Sea World?
Can we ever even go home again?
There is a way, but at this juncture,
I'm afraid it's no longer safe.
Your only hope for escape is
to make your way to Cloud End.
From there, you can travel home. Huh?
What's Cloud End?
And how are we supposed to get there?
It's a region that lies far to the east.
The only way for you to get there is
to travel across the White White Sea.
OK, so we sell east and
we eventually get home.
But I don't want to go home.
Your other option is stay and get
sentenced to death. Listen to me.
I don't want you causing any more
trouble for Conis and her dad.
No, don't worry about us.
Even if we leave right now, there's no
guarantee we'll make a clean escape.
We don't have any time to
lose, so just get on the ship!
You'll have your big adventure, I promise,
but right now we need to get going!
So come on, everybody, let's set sail!
Thanks for all your help!
We really appreciate it!
Ooh, hold on!
Come on, now what?
Hey, old man!
What is it, Luffy?
Can I ask a favor?
You mind if we take the
leftovers from earlier?
Of course not.
They're all yours.
Woo-hoo!
Come on, Sanji, make us lunch!
I'm glad you got priorities.
In that case, could I ask for
a teensy little favor, too?
You're an engineer, right?
I don't suppose you could spare
any parts or tools to fix our ship.
What's mine is yours, Usopp.
Feel free to take anything you need.
Uh, guys?
Where are you going?
Hello?
They got food!
Tell you what, you go ahead and
ready the ship for departure,
and we'll be back before you know it.
He's dead set on going to that island.
Doesn't he get it?
Don't take it out on us.
You know how he is.
Seriously, try to relax.
Chopper, you're still
on my side, aren't you?
Aren't you?
Don't answer that.
Heavy, quick!
I was about to drop the
ladder for you, you know.
You know there's no
persuading Luffy of anything!
He won't listen, even if
we all gang up on him.
Fine, then I guess I'll just stay put.
Well, you're free to do whatever you want.
I know that!
But if I stay here, I'll be killed!
Yep.
Quite a predicament.
Jerk!
Robin, let's go beat
some sense into Luffy.
Won't work.
I guess we'd have a better
chance against the white berets.
And you know they've already got to be
gathering reinforcements to follow us.
Follow you, idiots.
Inaru and his priest
aren't going anywhere.
Why should I bother when
your true judgment awaits?
Once you weigh anchor,
your challenge will begin.
Your ship will set its own course
to the forbidden sacred grounds.
The Upper Yard.
Mmm, this is really good.
Save some for the trip,
and for the rest of us.
There's plenty here, so I hold back.
This does have to feed all of us!
Conis! Refill!
Why don't you get it yourself?
Speaking of, where is Conis?
I think she went to bid
farewell to the others.
Oh I brought you some more tea!
So you're the shipwright
for your vessel, aren't you?
Well, not really, actually I'm a sniper.
Wow, that sounds exciting!
Yeah, I guess so, but it means we don't
have a regular ship ride in our crew.
Let's see, how can I put this delicately?
I am cursed with supreme skill on every
subject, and the whole crew relies on me!
Yeah, it's a lot of work, but without
me, the ship just wouldn't function.
My official title is sharpshooter,
but I'm also the co-captain.
And that's why everyone calls me...
Captain!
Oh, your color arrangement clearly
denotes the work of a professional.
Of course.
I consider the plating
of food an art form.
No, that doesn't work.
Throws off the whole arrangement.
If I put the red one here and then the
emerald green broad beans across the back...
Oh, no, this looks delicious.
I sure hope Nami and Robin
appreciate the hard work.
Wow, it doesn't even look like food.
I've never seen such a
beautifully prepared lunch before.
Here. Really?
I made one for you as well. Really?
Custom-made just for me?
I've prepared all the food today
according to a theme I've chosen.
I call it Love is a Cruel Mistress,
Feast for a Fallen Angel. I see.
I don't get what all the fuss is.
It's just a box lunch.
How dare you trash my work!
You better watch your mouth!
A great meal starts
with great presentation!
Why bother?
It all comes out the same.
You're stuffing your face
without even looking!
Yeah, and?
Why are you so mad if
this doesn't taste good?
Because food should please your
eyes as well as your palate.
Hey!
Something's wrong with this ship.
Huh?
What is it? Take a look.
She just started rocking all of a sudden.
Really?
Hope they're not having a party
without us. Hey, look. It's Nami.
Wait.
Why in the world is she wearing a t-shirt?
I'm pretty sure we have more
pressing concerns right now!
Guys, look!
The ship started moving!
But why?
They wouldn't just leave
us here, would they?
Whoa!
I don't think I've ever seen a
ship sailing backwards before!
But they haven't even
set the sails yet! Huh?
There's something underneath!
I think we're being dragged away.
But by what?
It must be.
It's the legendary White White
Sea Super Express monster.
Guys, we're being hijacked.
We'll have to abandon ship.
Come on, we've got to move right
now while we still have time.
We can't leave the ship.
Without it, we won't be
able to get back home.
Then I'll stay behind. Just go now.
Forget it!
You can't defend the whole
ship by yourself! I'll manage!
All right, making progress.
I don't think that'll get you anywhere.
Come back on board.
Why should I?
You'll never be able to
significantly damage that creature,
and we've got bigger problems now.
Look! What?
A school of vicious skyfish are
following us, ready to attack.
We can't jump ship and escape now.
Even if we manage to defeat the skyfish,
I'm sure that more will
arrive to take their place.
Our punishment has already begun,
and there's no way to stop it.
Heaven's judgment.
They must be taking us
to the Forbidden Island.
Guess they got tired of waiting.
Hunter has really got it in for us.
Oh, no.
Please, I can't go back there.
Luffy!
Help us!
Saji!
Why, Nami?
Why a t-shirt?
You're still thinking of that?
This is awful, Luffy.
What are we going to do?
We have to rescue Nami and the others.
Hmm. I wonder.
Where are they going?
Yes, right.
I got nothing.
Um, well... Huh? Huh?
The Super Express Lobster
is a messenger of Eneru.
He must be taking your friends
as a sacrificial offering.
If that's the case,
they are being taken to the Northeast
Upper Yard to the sacrificial altar.
Say what?
You don't mean that Nami
and Robin and the rest
are going to be sacrificed
to that wannabe god?
That bastard better not harm a
single hair on my pretty Nami's head.
But listen carefully, because I have
not yet told you what else will happen.
What, there's more? You see,
in Heaven's Judgment, there are actually
two different types of criminal punishment,
and I've only told you about the first.
The second punishment is a challenge.
Your friends are currently
hostages in Anaru's hands,
and they are being taken
to him even as we speak.
Hostages?
I'm afraid I must tell you,
the criminals who are
to receive the judgment
are the three of you standing before me.
Wait, what are you trying to say?
If we only had a map.
Uh, I know I've got one of
Skype here with me somewhere.
Well, this one is very old,
but it looks like the general shape
of the island is correctly rendered.
This is where we are now.
The sacrificial altar
where your friends are
headed is located a good
distance to the northeast,
here in the upper yard.
And I'm afraid there's
only one way to get there.
You have to take the milky
road that leaves this island,
and your only means of
transportation will be the waiver.
The road will take you to a great forest
where the priests are
awaiting your arrival.
Well, let's see.
There's got to be a better way
for us to get there unnoticed.
If we just ride up to the front
gate, we won't stand a chance.
Couldn't we sneak around the side?
Usopp's right.
If we take the main road, they'll
see us coming and set a track.
That may be, but even if
you do find your way ashore,
there's no way that you'll ever
make it to the altar on foot.
You see,
your old map differs from
the current configuration in
that now the Milky Roads
crisscross the entire island.
The cloud canals you mentioned. Correct.
There are hundreds of them of all
sizes running every which way.
I don't think anyone really
knows where they all lead.
Hmm, I see.
That's why your only course
of action is, as I've said?
You must follow the main
milky road to the island.
and from there continue
until you reach the altar.
Is that so?
And even if we do find another way ashore,
the canals will block us
from continuing inland.
That's right.
Did I mention the man-eating
fish that prowl the canal?
Man-eating fish?
Sounds like they covered all their bases.
So you're saying if we want
our friends and ship back,
We have to walk right up to
their front door and march on it.
This is part of the
challenge you mentioned?
Part of Heaven's judgment?
Yes.
In Upper Yard,
there are four powerful priests of
unimaginable strength who await you.
Sounds like a piece of cake.
I mean, all we have to do to get our friends
back is beat up these priests, right?
You make it sound easy.
Finally, a little action!
Whoa!
This place is great!
Lovely Street is the center
of commerce on the island.
It has everything.
Check it out, floating stores!
It takes a special variety of
Island Cloud to build those.
So, where's all the floating restaurants?
Hey guys, I notice everyone's
avoiding us. Again,
can't say I blame them or it's probably
already gotten out that we're criminals.
So what else is new?
Let him be that way that means
we've got downtown all to
ourselves all these gorgeous
angels and they're avoiding me
Sure is a lot of weird
stuff for sale here.
Oh
Man, I don't have any money. Hey
mister. Do you take treasure?
Hey,
Luffy, when you're done fooling around,
there's still the matter of
rescuing Nami and the others.
If you don't get serious, and soon,
they're going to be sacrificed.
Do you know that?
You worry too much. They're fine.
Don't forget, Zoro's with them.
Yeah, like we can really
count on that guy.
I just hope the ship hasn't
sustained any more damage.
I mean, she's had more than
her share of abuse lately.
Huh.
There's something in the
middle of the street.
Huh?
What a weird face.
What's it supposed to be a seal looks like
a figure made out of
mud knowing this place?
I bet it's some kind of religious statue.
Oh, you're both morons. This is art.
I can tell this is birth
You might see it represents the eternal
yearnings of the people of the sky
Fourth, huh? Really?
So what you guys like pray to this thing?
That's pretty crazy.
Well, I guess it would be difficult for
someone from the Blue Sea to understand.
Oh, we're almost to the
docks, right this way?
Aw, we're leaving town already? Already?
We were never planning on stopping
here in the first place I know,
but I don't see why we couldn't
stick around a little bit longer
Look at all these boats!
Yes, you'll notice there are boats of all
shapes and sizes anchored in this harbor.
Whoa that one it's perfect.
I always wanted a gondola
we'll take it oh look
back there i bet those
dials make this baby move.
Quicker than lightning
this is gonna be a whole
lot of fun come on let's
go for a spin you idiot.
We've got to rescue the
crew first remember get
serious will you actually
your boat is right over here.
Great is it even awesomer than the
gondola man I can't wait to see it.
Presenting the crow you're kidding me
right wait crows don't even swim I only.
I learned to ride a waver recently.
Before then, I used
the crow to get around.
It's not as fast as a waver, of course,
but it has two breath dials
and is quite reliable.
Please, feel free to use it.
Wait.
I'm not going.
Aha.
I knew he'd finally show his true colors.
Unless I can take that!
He's not scared, he's selfish.
That one, huh?
You don't like the crow? I'm sorry.
The only thing sorry is this guy.
Apologize, you ingrate.
She goes through the trouble of getting
us a boat and all you do is complain.
What's wrong with you?
I'm sorry he doesn't appreciate
your help like I do, Conis.
I'm sorry.
Your exit is gate number two.
It leads right to the Milky Road, and that
will take you all the way to Upper Yard.
Just...
just follow it and you'll be fine.
Hey, Conis.
Yes?
You've been trembling ever since we left.
Is everything okay?
Can't hear.
What are they talking about?
Is it that noticeable?
Yeah.
It's like you're scared or something.
No, wait.
She wouldn't.
Don't you get it?
She's worried about us.
Oh, Conis, that is so
sweet of you, my dear.
Speaking of being worried, are you
and Pagaya going to be all right?
I mean, everyone in town is
avoiding us like the plague,
but you're leading us around, lending
us your boat, giving us directions.
Is helping us going to get you in trouble?
Doesn't that make you,
like, our accomplices?
Conis, don't cry.
You're gonna be fine, Kay.
You should have told us you were scared.
Really.
We could have just come here on our own.
No, it's...
it's not...
it's not what you think.
She wouldn't dare.
Don't say anything you'll regret.
it.
Don't you get it?
Even after I told you how terrifying
Upper Yard is, I still led you here.
I even got you a boat and
told you which route to take.
Don't you find that odd?
Isn't
it obvious what's going on here?
God.
Watch your tongue, little girl.
Don't say anything
foolish.
You hear something?
Don't tell me they're all in on this.
It's every citizen's duty.
You know what will happen if we
don't follow almighty Eneru's will?
Just run away. Please.
I'm so sorry, you guys.
No, no, stop!
What do you think you're doing?
I called the Super Express Lobster.
It was all my fault.
You mean that thing that took
Nami and the others away?
You called it, Conis?
While you three were inside
talking to my father,
I went aboard and lied to your friends
about a current that leads to Cloud End.
They believed me, and I
had them raise anchor.
That was the signal that summoned
almighty Anaru Super Express Lobster.
What?
Do you want to die?
You stupid girl.
Once we know someone's a criminal,
we must lead them to Upper Yard.
If we don't, then the penalty is death.
You idiot.
You're going to bring his
wrath down upon us all.
This is outrageous.
Somebody stop her.
It's our duty.
The duty of every citizen.
That's crazy. I know.
I'm sorry.
I should have told you sooner.
Wait a sec.
You're saying they forced
you to lead us all here?
If that's true...
Then why even tell us at all?
Are you nuts?
Now your life is in danger!
It's all over.
We're too late.
Get away from the girl.
The judgment is coming.
It's too big!
Let's go.
What in the world was that thing?
It did that?
Luffy! Conis! Where are you?
Conis!
Luffy! Conis!
That's what happens to those
who defy almighty Eneru.
Do not fear.
They are both safe.
It's him, Gonfall.
Oh, the weird old man.
Me, weird? No.
I am the Sky Knight, friend,
and this one's on the house.
Tunis, look, she's safe.
And she will remain so under my watch.
You have my word, I shan't
allow Eneru to harm her!
Thanks.
Now that you've seen the
scope of Eneru's power.
And anger?
What are you going to do next?
The same thing we were
going to do from the start.
Go to Upperyard and rescue our friends!
I see may luck be with you.
What about them they have chosen their
own course do not blame yourself child I!
Know who you really are.
Of course, it's no secret.
I am the Sky Knight. No, it's...
We all know.
Please come back to us.
God.
Good luck, fellas.
Hop aboard, get comfy.
I'll give you a good shove-off.
Get on the boat.
I don't wanna.
All right, Upper Yard, here we come.
They went, without any fear or hesitation.